So this is very positive. You know, one of the reasons why the United States government has
continued to have the power to really just do whatever the corporations want it to do while
ignoring the people is because so often the people put all of our energy into expecting
our representatives to do the things. And the system itself does not make demands of
the representatives to do anything. So this is really great news. Hearing that Zoran Mamdani
is going to start a 501c4 called Our Time for the purpose of mobilizing supporters to pass his
agenda. So when I said on my show Views for Amandaland that the win of Zoran Mamdani was
the people, I just want to always remind us that we are the win. Zoran Mamdani won the
mayorship of New York because of the people. Because the people elected him based on the
things that matter to the people. The people elected somebody who didn't take Israeli lobby
money. He didn't take money from big oil. And it was the people that said, OK, this is
what we want, even though y'all are trying to propagandize us. However, we have seen that
in the past. And then what happens is that the people are kind of like, OK, where do we go
now? Or they're just like, let's go back to brunch. In this case, no excuses for brunch
choices. Because there is going to be an organization ready and waiting for you to make demands of
the person that you have elected. And it was created by the person that you've elected.
So I love seeing this. This is a very great move in the right direction. And it is very
socialistic. I am Claire Stump. Right ahead call the girls like, what y'all wearing to
the march? What y'all wearing to the march? I tell her, I was MC Checkerho. But now I'm
your father. Oh, chill baby, chill.